softwarelode.com 2013-04-30

# SoftwareLode - Privacy Statement

**Information Collection and Use**

When a visitor requests pages from SoftwareLode site, our Web Server automatically recognizes Browser Name and Version, User OS, User IP address, Path etc. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals.

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information that is sent by a web server to be stored on a web browser cache in plain text format, so that it can later be read back from that browser when this visitor returns to that web server. This becomes useful for keeping you logged in your personal account unless you log out, tracking your travel over a particular site, remembering user preferences etc. Cookies cannot be used to retrieve personal data from your hard drive, install a virus, get your email address, or steal sensitive information about who you are. You do not need to have cookies turned on to navigate through our site.  
We use cookies for the following purposes: 

  * Keeping count of return visits;
  * Tracking downloads with affiliate partnership support to receive our affiliate commission if user decides to purchase the software later, after downloading and trying it;

We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on SoftwareLode site to use tracking technologies. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Our advertisers' use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies, and we do not have any access to this information.

**Links to Other Resources**

SoftwareLode web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us via contact form.
